bestsearching.com 2008-11-20

# Best Searching Privacy Policy

****   
 **Privacy Policy**

Best Space Corporation, (Best Searching) owns and operates a number of different sites on the Web (each, an "Best Searching Site"). Best Searching is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its user community. The intent of this privacy policy is to detail the information Best Searching may gather about individuals who visit the Best Searching Sites, how that information is used, and Best Searching's disclosure practices. Please note that this policy applies only to the Best Searching Sites, and not to the Web sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links or to any software that may be downloaded from the Best Searching Sites. 

**Anonymous User Information**

Best Searching collects some anonymous information each time you visit a Best Searching Site so we can improve the overall quality of your online experience. We collect your IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type. You do not have to register with Best Searching before we can collect this anonymous information. 

The Best Searching Sites do not require you to share information that identifies you personally, such as your name or e-mail address, in order for you to use the Best Searching Sites. The Best Searching Sites assign an anonymous ID number to your requests and links the following additional data to that number: the date and time you visited the Best Searching Site, your search terms, and the links upon which you choose to click. Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files to collect and store this anonymous user information. Best Searching analyzes the information to examine trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

**Individual User Information**

From time-to-time the Best Searching Sites request information from you that may identify you personally in addition to the anonymous information described above. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name, e-mail address, shipping address, and zip code), and demographic information (such as age, gender, occupation, and household income). Best Searching will not use or disclose your individual user information except as mentioned in this privacy policy. Best Searching collects individual user information in the following ways from different Best Searching Sites. 

**Surveys or Contests**

From time to time, Best Searching may conduct surveys or contests on an Best Searching Site. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose individual user information to the Best Searching Site. Contest information will be shared with the contest or survey sponsors to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Best Searching Site. We may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests. These companies may use your personal information to help the Best Searching Site communicate with you about offers from the Best Searching Site and our marketing partners. Such third parties do not have Best Searching's permission to use your personally identifiable information for any secondary purpose. 

**Directory Services**

Best Searching offers certain personalization services within its directory services (i.e., White Pages and Yellow Pages) that enable you to give us your geographic location so we can remember it for you when you return to use our service. For example, if we know that you are searching from Boston, Massachusetts for a particular company, we will pre-populate the city and state fields with Boston and Massachusetts. While you are not required to use this feature of the directory services, the information enables us to provide you with a more efficient experience on the Best Searching Sites. In addition, Best Searching allows you to update, correct any errors in the listings, or include yourself in the directory services. In order to make these modifications, you may provide Best Searching with certain individual user information that Best Searching will use, along with its affiliates and third party service providers, to modify and update your information in the directory services database. 

Yellow Pages listings are supplied by Verizon SuperPages. To add or update your existing free basic Yellow Pages listing, please go to the following web site: 

_https://snap.superpages.com/NASApp/Listing/control/ViewListing_.   
To delete your listing, please call the customer service department at 1-800-428-8722, stay on the line without pushing any prompts, and a representative will assist you. 

You may update or delete your White Pages listing by searching the White Pages or contacting us to find your listing. Once you have located it, simply email us to update or remove link. To verify your request, Best Searching will send an e-mail message to the address that you provide. Once you confirm the request, your listing will be updated or deleted. Please allow approximately 24 hours for the update to become active after we receive your confirmation. 

**User Groups**

When you register for a user group on any of the Best Searching Sites, you are asked for your individual user information. The individual user information may be collected and stored by a third party partner. This partner will store your individual user information on their servers for a period of time at which Best Searching will assume such storage responsibilities and your information will be deleted from their servers. The partner will not have Best Searching's permission to use your individual user information for secondary purposes. If you choose to participate in a user group, your individual user information will be used to qualify you and to contact you for various projects at Best Searching's discretion. Best Searching may share your individual user information with a third party with whom Best Searching has entered into an agreement to support such user group projects. You may opt out at any time by following the opt out provisions of this privacy policy. 

**Tell-A-Friend**

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about any of our sites, we ask you for your friend's name and e-mail address. Best Searching will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the Best Searching Site. Best Searching does not store the information related to your friends and the one-time e-mail sent pursuant to your input will be our only contact with that person for such input. 

**Correspondence**

If you contact Best Searching, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your e-mail address. 

**Third Party Information Gathering**

The Best Searching Sites include content and ads from third parties that may perform user activity tracking other than that described herein. For more information about each third party content provider, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please refer to such third party advertiser's privacy policy. 

The Best Searching Sites contain links to other sites on the Web. Please be aware that Best Searching is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Cookies**

Best Searching may set and access Best Searching or partner cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small data file that a Web site may send to your browser and which may then be stored on your system. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For the session cookie, once you close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

We use cookie and web beacon technology to track which pages on the Best Searching Sites our visitors view and which Web browsers our visitors use. We may also use cookies to help us provide personalized features and preferences to you within various Best Searching Sites in a way that may be linked to individual user information that you elect to share with us. We also use "action tags" to assist in delivering the cookie. These action tags allow us to compile statistics and other data about our customers on an aggregate basis, by embedding a random identifying number on each user's browser. Then we track where that number shows up on our site. 

**Sharing**

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Best Searching's or such Best Searching Site's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

Best Searching Sites may use third party service providers to serve ads and e-mails on our behalf. These companies may use technologies to measure the effectiveness of ads and e-mails and use information about your visits to the Best Searching Site so that we can provide a better search experience to you. For this purpose, we may also provide this third party service provider anonymous information about your site navigation. 

**Mergers; Business Transitions**

In the event Best Searching goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, become part of the assets transferred. 

**Choice/Opt-out**

We desire to keep you in control of the personal information you provide to us. Accordingly, you can review, correct, change or remove the personal registration information you provide to Best Searching and that Best Searching controls. In order to elect not to receive future communications from us, please email us at 

_privacy@bestsearching.com_. 

If you have questions about public record information available through the Public Records service, please go to the following web site for additional information: 

_http://www.bestsearching/contactus.com_.

 **Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement in places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If, however, we are going to use Individually Identifiable Information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days. 

**Special Notification with respect to Children's Privacy (Users under the age of 13)**

In response to concerns about protecting children's privacy online, Congress enacted the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), which sets forth rules and procedures governing the ways in which Web sites may collect, use and disclose any personal information for children under the age of 13. In accordance with Best Searching policy and COPPA regulations, we DO NOT: 

1\. Request or knowingly collect personally identifiable information online or offline contact information from users under 13 years of age; or 

2\. Knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 years of age with third parties. 

It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information from our servers 

Questions regarding children's privacy should be directed to: 

Best Space Corporation  
274 Main Street, Suite 307  
Reading, MA 01867  
\+ (1) 781.942.0200 phone  
\+ (1) 781.942.7707 fax   
E-mail: 

_[kidsprivacy@bestsearching.com](mailto:kidsprivacy@bestsearching.com)_

Policy effective January 1, 2008
